A Guide to the Papers of Julian Bond, 1897-2006
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Series III: Organizations
  - The African-American Institute- The African-American Dialogue Remarks and Statements, 1973 December (Box-folder 37:3)
  - Alliance for Labor Action, 1969 (Box-folder 37:4)
  - American Civil Liberties Union, 1967-1977 (Box-folder 37:5)
  - American Civil Liberties Union- Directories, 1973-1976 (Box-folder 37:6)
  - American Civil Liberties Union- Lawyers Constitutional Defense Committees, 1969 (Box-folder 37:7)
  - American Civil Liberties Union- Prison Law Project, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 37:8)
  - American Hospital Association, 1971 (Box-folder 37:9)
  - Atlanta Black Draft Advisors, 1971 (Box-folder 37:10)
  - The Atlanta Committee to End the War in Vietnam, 1966, n.d. (Box-folder 37:11)
  - Atlanta Region Metropolitan Planning Commission, 1966 (Box-folder 37:12)
  - Atlanta University Center, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 37:13)
  - Atlanta University Center Civil Rights Movement 1960-1990 Anniversary, 1990 (Box-folder 37:14)
  - B Organizations, 1971-1976 (Box-folder 38:1)
  - Black American Law Students Association (BALSA), 1969-1970 (Box-folder 38:2)
  - Black Economic Development Council, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 38:3)
  - Black Economic Research Center, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 38:4)
  - Black Educational Services, Inc, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 38:5)
  - Black Enterprise, 1969-1973, 1977 (Box-folder 38:6)
  - Black Marines of New Jersey, 1976 (Box-folder 38:7)
  - Black Radical Congress, 1998 June 19-21 (Box-folder 38:8)
  - Black-Pac, Inc. (Black Political Action Committee), 1980-1982 (Box-folder 38:9)
  - Butterfly Youth Foundation- Summers in the South Proposal, 1975 (Box-folder 38:10)
  - C Organizations, 1968-1977 (Box-folder 38:11)
  - Center for Community Change, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 38:12)
  - Center for Community Change, 1971 (Box-folder 38:13)
  - Center for Democratic Renewal, 1998 (Box-folder 38:14)
  - Center for Responsible Lending, 2002-2004 (Box-folder 38:15)
  - Citizens Board of Inquiry into Health Services for Americans, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 39:1)
  - Citizens Board of Inquiry into Health Services for Americans, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 39:2)
  - Citizens Board of Inquiry into Health Services for Americans- Report, 1971 (Box-folder 39:3)
  - Citizen's Commission on Civil Rights, 1996, 2001 (Box-folder 39:4)
  - Commission for Racial Justice, 1971-1973, 1977 (Box-folder 39:5)
  - Committee for Community Affairs, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 39:6)
  - Common Cause, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 39:7)
  - Community Education and Action Organization- Proposal, 1968, n.d. (Box-folder 39:8)
  - Community Relations Commission, 1968-1971 (Box-folder 39:9)
  - Congress of African People, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 39:10)
  - Congressional Action Fund, 1972 (Box-folder 39:11)
  - Constituency for Africa (CFA), 2004 (Box-folder 39:12)
  - Cornerstone Project, Inc., 1969 (Box-folder 39:13)
  - D through F Organizations, 1966, 1970-1977 (Box-folder 40:1)
  - The Delta Ministry, 1969 (Box-folder 40:2)
  - Eldridge Cleaver Defense Committee, 1975-1977 (Box-folder 40:3)
  - The Eleanor Roosevelt Papers- Honorary Advisory Board, 2001 (Box-folder 40:4)
  - Federal Communications Commission, 1967-1968, 1975 (Box-folder 40:5)
  - Federation of Southern Cooperatives, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 40:6)
  - Free Southern Theater, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 40:7)
  - Free Southern Theater, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 40:8)
  - Freedom to Marry, 2004 (Box-folder 40:9)
  - G through J Organizations, 1967-1976 (Box-folder 40:10)
  - Georgia Association for Black Elected Officials, 1977 (Box-folder 40:11)
  - Georgia Council on Human Relations, 1968-1971 (Box-folder 40:12)
  - Georgia Student Rural Project-Proposal, n.d. (Box-folder 40:13)
  - Govolution- Board of Advisors, 2000 (Box-folder 40:14)
  - Harvard Business School's Initiative on Social Enterprise, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 41:1)
  - Harvard Business School's Initiative on Social Enterprise- Advisory Board, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 41:2)
  - Highlander Research and Education Center, 1968-1973 (Box-folder 41:3)
  - Institute for Southern Studies, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 41:4)
  - The Institute of the Black World, 1971-1976 (Box-folder 41:5)
  - The International Eye Foundation, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 41:6)
  - Isaac Hayes Foundation, 1971 (Box-folder 41:7)
  - Job Corps Center, Atlanta, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 41:8)
  - Joint Center for Political Studies, 1970-1977 (Box-folder 41:9)
  - Joint Center for Urban Environmental Studies, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 41:10)
  - L through M Organizations, 1969-1976 (Box-folder 41:11)
  - Leadership Conference on Civil Rights, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 42:1)
  - Legal Education Grants to Assist Minorities, Inc., 1972 (Box-folder 42:2)
  - The Martin Luther King, Jr. Memorial Center, 1968-1973 (Box-folder 42:3)
  - Mary Holmes College Fund, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 42:4)
  - The Mary McLeod Bethune Memorial Committee, 1970 (Box-folder 42:5)
  - Medgar Evers Instititute, 2004 (Box-folder 42:6)
  - Metropolitan Applied Research Center, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 42:7)
  - Metropolitan Atlanta Association for the Blind, Inc., 1972-1973 (Box-folder 42:8)
  - Metropolitan Atlanta Rapid Transit Authority (MARTA), 1973, 1977, 1979 (Box-folder 42:9)
  - Morehouse College, 1968-1979 (Box-folder 42:10)
  - N Organizations, 1970-1976 (Box-folder 42:11)
  - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (hereafter abbreviated as NAACP), 1969-1977 (Box-folder 42:12)
  - NAACP- Abortion and Blacks, 2003-2004, n.d. (Box-folder 43:1)
  - NAACP- Advocacy and Policy Committee, [2005], n.d. (Box-folder 43:2)
  - NAACP- Afro-Academic, Cultural, Technological and Scientific Olympics (ACT-SO), 1996-1998, n.d. (Box-folder 43:3)
  - NAACP- Articles and News clippings, 1983-2004, n.d. (Box-folder 43:4)
  - NAACP- Articles and News clippings, 1999 July 18, Matted and oversize. (Box-folder 43)
    One New York Daily News clipping about Julian Bond and Kweisi Mfume.
  - NAACP- Atlanta Branch, 1977 January-May (Box-folder 43:5)
  - NAACP- Atlanta Branch, 1977 June-December (Box-folder 43:6)
  - NAACP- Awards and Scholarship Committee, 1996, n.d. (Box-folder 43:7)
  - NAACP- Board of Directors, 1987-2005 (Box-folder 43:8)
  - NAACP- Board of Directors - Minutes, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 43:9)
  - NAACP- Board of Directors- Retreats and Self-Assessments, 1996-2000 (Box-folder 43:10)
  - NAACP- Board of Directors- Retreats and Self-Assessments, 2002-2005 (Box-folder 43:11)
  - NAACP- Board of Directors- Terms of Service, 2003 (Box-folder 43:12)
  - NAACP- Branches and Chapters, 1995-2000 (Box-folder 43:13)
  - NAACP- Campaign Finance Litigation and Reform, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 44:1)
  - NAACP- Campaign Finance Litigation and Reform, 1999-2001, n.d. (Box-folder 44:2)
  - NAACP- Centennial Program Taskforce, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 44:3)
  - NAACP- Chairmanship of Julian Bond, 1998-2003 (Box-folder 44:4)
  - NAACP- Chief Executive Assessments, 1997-2004 (Box-folder 44:5)
  - NAACP- Code of Ethics, n.d. (Box-folder 44:6)
  - NAACP- Committees, 1998-2003 (Box-folder 44:7)
  - NAACP- Compensation Study Progress Report, 2001 (Box-folder 44:8)
  - NAACP- Confederate Flag Protest and Boycott, 1999 (Box-folder 44:9)
  - NAACP- Constitution, 1996-2000 (Box-folder 44:10)
  - NAACP- Corporate Reorganization, 1996-2004 (Box-folder 44:11)
  - NAACP-Correspondence, 1989-2005 (Box-folder 44:12)
    Correspondents include: Benjamin L. Hooks and Myrlie Evers-Williams.
  - NAACP- Correspondence congratulating Bond on his Chairmanship, 1998, Including: Congressman Dick Armey, William Cohen, Senator Paul Coverdell, Congressman Elijah E. Cummings, Elizabeth Dole, Governor Parris N. Glendening, Senator J. Robert Kerry, Coretta Scott King, Congressman John Lewis, Senator Joseph I. Lieberman, Senator Howard M. Metzenbaum, Carol Moseley-Braun, Robert H. Schuller, Rodney E. Slater, Governor Christine Todd Whitman. (Box-folder 44:13)
  - NAACP- The Crisis, 1993-1996 February (Box-folder 45:1)
  - NAACP- The Crisis, 1996 March-1999 (Box-folder 45:2)
  - NAACP- The Crisis, 2000-2005 (Box-folder 45:3)
  - NAACP- The Crisis Seattle Branch Freedom Fund Banquet, 2004 (Box-folder 45:4)
  - NAACP- Death Penalty, 2001 (Folder 45:5)
  - NAACP- Development Office Packet, 2005 (Box-folder 45:6)
  - NAACP- Economic Reciprocity Initiative, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 45:7)
  - NAACP- Employee Handbook, 1997, 2004 (Box-folder 45:8)
  - NAACP- Environment, 2003-2005 (Box-folder 45:9)
  - NAACP- Foreign Affairs, 1997 (Box-folder 45:10)
  - NAACP- Fundraising, 1999-2003 (Box-folder 45:11)
  - NAACP-Gay Marriage, 1997-2004, n.d. (Box-folder 45:12)
  - NAACP- Dr. William F. Gibson, Controversy concerning, 1991-1994 November (Box-folder 46:1)
  - NAACP- Dr. William F. Gibson, Controversy concerning, 1994 Dec -1995, n.d. (Box-folder 46:2)
  - NAACP- Headquarters Operations, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 46:3)
  - NAACP- Headquarters Relocation, 1999-2002 (Box-folder 46:4)
  - NAACP- History (copies), 1914-1933 (Box-folder 46:5)
  - NAACP- History (copies), 1945-1977 (Box-folder 46:6)
  - NAACP- History (partial copies), 1983-2000, n.d. (Box-folder 46:7)
  - NAACP- HIV/AIDS, 1996-2004 (Box-folder 46:8)
  - NAACP- Image Awards, 2002-2004 (Box-folder 46:9)
  - NAACP- Information Packet, 2003 (Box-folder 46:10)
  - NAACP- Internal Revenue Service, 2003-2005 (Box-folder 47:1)
  - NAACP- Issue Organizing Center, 2001 (Box-folder 47:2)
  - NAACP- Leadership in the 21st Century, 1995-1998 (Box-folder 47:3)
  - NAACP- Meetup.com, 2003, n.d. (Box-folder 47:4)
  - NAACP- Membership, 1997-2000, n.d. (Box-folder 47:5)
  - NAACP- Memoranda, 1996-2002 (Box-folder 47:6)
  - NAACP- CEO Kweisi Mfume, Articles concerning, 2003-2005 (Box-folder 47:7)
  - NAACP- CEO Kweisi Mfume, Contract with, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 47:8)
  - NAACP- CEO Kweisi Mfume, Contract with, 2000-2001 April (Box-folder 47:9)
  - NAACP- CEO Kweisi Mfume, Contract with, 2001 June 2002 (Box-folder 47:10)
  - NAACP- CEO Kweisi Mfume, Contract with, 2003-2005, n.d. (Box-folder 47:11)
  - NAACP- CEO Kweisi Mfume, Resignation of, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 48:1)
  - NAACP- Miscellaneous, 1937-2004 (Box-folder 48:2)
  - NAACP- National Internet Program, 1996-2003 (Box-folder 48:3)
  - NAACP- National Voter Fund, 2000-2005 (Box-folder 48:4)
  - NAACP- National Voter Fund Final Media Report Part I- National Coverage, 2000 September-2001 January, Oversize white notebook. (Box-folder 48:4)
  - NAACP- National Voter Fund Final Media Report Part II- Regional Coverage, 2000 September-2001 January, Oversize white notebook. (Box-folder 48:4)
  - NAACP- National Voter Fund and the Presidential Election in Florida, 2000 (Box-folder 48:5)
  - NAACP- National Voter Fund Communications, 2000 (Box-folder 48:6)
  - NAACP- Payday Lending Issue, 2000-2005, n.d. (Box-folder 48:7)
  - NAACP- Policies, 1999-2004, n.d. (Box-folder 48:8)
  - NAACP- Programs, 1981-1998, n.d. (Box-folder 48:9)
  - NAACP- Religious Affairs, 1999, n.d. (Box-folder 48:10)
  - NAACP- Reports, 1996-1999 (Box-folder 48:11)
  - NAACP- Research, 1997-2002 (Box-folder 49:1)
  - NAACP- Resolutions, 1990-2000, n.d. (Box-folder 49:2)
  - NAACP- Review of the Financial Operations, 1996-1998 (Box-folder 49:3)
  - NAACP- Rules, n.d. (Box-folder 49:4)
  - NAACP- Soros, George and the Open Society Institute, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 49:5)
  - NAACP- Spingarn Medal, 1998-2000 (Box-folder 49:6)
  - NAACP- Statements and Remarks by Julian Bond, 1980-2005 (Box-folder 49:7)
  - NAACP- Strategic Measurements Taskforce, 2003 (Box-folder 49:8)
  - NAACP- Strategic Plan, 2000-2002 (Box-folder 49:9)
  - NAACP- Surveys, 1999, n.d. (Box-folder 49:10)
  - NAACP- Task Force on Africa Report and Recommendations, 1978 (Box-folder 49:11)
  - NAACP- Time Magazine Dispute, 2005 (Box-folder 49:12)
  - NAACP- Training, 1997-2000 (Box-folder 49:13)
  - NAACP- Unit Network Quick Reference Guides, n.d. (Box-folder 49:14)
  - NAACP- United Nations Recognition as a Non-Governmental Organization (NGO), 2001 (Box-folder 49:15)
  - NAACP- Volunteers, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 49:16)
  - NAACP- Voter Empowerment Expenses, 2000-2002 (Box-folder 49:17)
  - National Black Economic Development Conference, 1969, n.d. (Box-folder 50:1)
  - National Business League, 1969 (Box-folder 50:2)
  - National Center for Appropriate Technology, 1998-1999, n.d. (Box-folder 50:3)
  - National Council of Negro Women, Inc., 1969, 1973, n.d. (Box-folder 50:4)
  - National Educational Conference of Black Mayors Resource and Research Advisory Committee and John Tyler, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 50:5)
  - National Movement for the Student Vote, 1971 (Box-folder 50:6)
  - National Public Radio, 1973 January-June (Box-folder 50:7)
  - National Public Radio, 1973 July-November (Box-folder 50:8)
  - National Public Radio-All Things Considered, 1972 (Box-folder 50:9)
  - National Rural Housing Coalition, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 50:10)
  - National Sharecroppers Fund, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 50:11)
  - National Sharecroppers Fund, 1971-1973, n.d. (Box-folder 50:12)
  - National Sharecroppers Fund, Inc.- Rural Advancement Fund, 1967-1973, n.d. (Box-folder 50:13)
  - National Urban Coalition, 1968-1971 June (Box-folder 51:1)
  - National Urban Coalition, 1971 July-1973, n.d. (Box-folder 51:2)
  - National Urban League, 1968-1969 June (Box-folder 51:3)
  - National Urban League, 1969 July-December (Box-folder 51:4)
  - National Urban League, 1970-2002, n.d. (Box-folder 51:5)
  - National Urban League- History, 1987-1989 (Box-folder 51:6)
  - Natural Resources Defense Council, Inc. (NRDC), 2004 (Box-folder 51:7)
  - The New Democratic Coalition, 1967-1974 (Box-folder 51:8)
  - O through R Organizations, 1969-2002, n.d. (Box-folder 51:9)
  - Organization of Afro-American Unity, 1996, n.d. (Box-folder 52:1)
  - Pacifica, 1969 (Box-folder 52:2)
  - Premier Automotive Group (PAG) Diversity Council, 1999-2001 (Box-folder 52:3)
  - Premier Automotive Group (PAG) Diversity Council, 2002-2005, n.d. (Box-folder 52:4)
  - Race Relations Institute, 1996-1997, n.d. (Box-folder 52:5)
  - Referendum 70, 1970 (Box-folder 52:6)
  - Robert F. Kennedy Memorial, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 52:7)
  - Robert F. Kennedy Memorial, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 52:8)
  - S through V Organizations, 1970-1977 (Box-folder 52:9)
  - Scholarship, Education, & Defense Fund for Racial Equality, 1969-1970 September (Box-folder 52:10)
  - Scholarship, Education, & Defense Fund for Racial Equality, 1970 October-1973 (Box-folder 52:11)
  - Sex Information and Education Council of the United States (SIECUS), 1969-1970 (Box-folder 53:1)
  - Songmasters-The American Road, 2000 (Box-folder 53:2)
  - South Atlantic Regional Humanities Center, 2001 (Box-folder 53:3)
  - Southern Center for Studies in Public Policy, 1969-1977 (Box-folder 53:4)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference, 1963-1988, n.d. (Box-folder 53:5)
  - Southern Conference Educational Fund, 1968-1973, n.d. (Box-folder 53:6)
  - Southern Elections Fund- Correspondence, 1968-1972 (Box-folder 53:7)
  - Southern Elections Fund- Correspondence, 1973 (Box-folder 53:8)
  - Southern Elections Fund- Correspondence, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 53:9)
  - Southern Elections Fund- Correspondence with Trustees and Staff, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 53:10)
  - Southern Elections Fund- Correspondence with Trustees and Staff, 1973-1977 (Box-folder 53:11)
  - Southern Elections Fund- Financial, 1971-1981 (Box-folder 54:1)
  - Southern Elections Fund- Proceedings and Minutes, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 54:2)
  - Southern Elections Fund- Proceedings and Minutes, 1974-1977, n.d. (Box-folder 54:3)
  - Southern Elections Fund- Publicity, 1969-1974, n.d. (Box-folder 54:4)
  - Southern Poverty Law Center, 1971 (Box-folder 54:5)
  - Southern Poverty Law Center, 1972 (Box-folder 54:6)
  - Southern Poverty Law Center, 1973 (Box-folder 54:7)
  - Southern Poverty Law Center, 1974-1975 May (Box-folder 55:1)
  - Southern Poverty Law Center, 1975 June-October (Box-folder 55:2)
  - Southern Poverty Law Center, 1976 January-August (Box-folder 55:3)
  - Southern Poverty Law Center, 1976 September-December (Box-folder 55:4)
  - Southern Poverty Law Center, 1977 January-March (Box-folder 55:5)
  - Southern Poverty Law Center, 1977 April-December (Box-folder 55:6)
  - Southern Poverty Law Center, 2002, n.d. (Box-folder 55:7)
  - Southern Poverty Law Center- Lawsuit concerning the issue of Sterilization of Indigent Minors by Federally Funded Agencies, 1973 (Box-folder 55:8)
  - Southern Regional Council, 1967-1970 (Box-folder 56:1)
  - Southern Regional Council, 1971-1976 (Box-folder 56:2)
  - Southern Regional Council, 1994-1996 (Box-folder 56:3)
  - Southern Regional Council, 1997 February-September (Box-folder 56:4)
  - Southern Regional Council, 1997 November-1998 (Box-folder 56:5)
  - Southern Regional Council- Reports concerning Sit-Ins, 1960-1998 (Box-folder 56:6)
  - Southern Student Organizing Committee, 1963-1994, n.d. (Box-folder 56:7)
  - Student Nonviolent Coordinating Committee (SNCC)- Anti-Vietnam War Statement, [1965?] (Box-folder 56:8)
  - Student Nonviolent Coordinating Committee (SNCC)- Archives on Deposit at the Martin Luther King Center, 1997 (Box-folder 56:9)
  - Student Nonviolent Coordinating Committee (SNCC)- Biographies, 1993, n.d. (Box-folder 56:10)
  - Student Nonviolent Coordinating Committee (SNCC) -Controversy concerning the Permanent Repository for its Papers, 1997 (Box-folder 56:11)
  - Student Nonviolent Coordinating Committee (SNCC)- Correspondence, 1963-1977 (Box-folder 56:12)
  - Student Nonviolent Coordinating Committee (SNCC)- Faculty Fund chaired by Dr. Horace Mann Bond, 1966 (Box-folder 57:1)
  - Student Nonviolent Coordinating Committee (SNCC)- Founding of the Organization, 1960, 2000 (Box-folder 57:2)
  - Student Nonviolent Coordinating Committee (SNCC)- Freedom of Information Act Request Copies, 1967-1968, 1 of 7 folders. (Box-folder 57:3)
  - Student Nonviolent Coordinating Committee (SNCC) - Freedom of Information Act Request Copies, 1964-1969, 2 of 7 folders. (Box-folder 57:4)
  - Student Nonviolent Coordinating Committee (SNCC)- Freedom of Information Act Request Copies, n.d., 3 of 7 folders. (Box-folder 57:5)
  - Student Nonviolent Coordinating Committee (SNCC)- Freedom of Information Act Request Copies, 1962 August-1963, 4 of 7 folders. (Box-folder 57:6)
  - Student Nonviolent Coordinating Committee (SNCC)- Freedom of Information Act Request Copies, 1964, 5 of 7 folders. (Box-folder 57:7)
  - Student Nonviolent Coordinating Committee (SNCC)- Freedom of Information Act Request Copies, 1965-1967, 6 of 7 folders. (Box-folder 57:8)
  - Student Nonviolent Coordinating Committee (SNCC)- Freedom of Information Act Request Copies, 1968-1969, 7 of 7 folders. (Box-folder 57:9)
  - Student Nonviolent Coordinating Committee (SNCC)- Freedom Summer, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 58:1)
  - Student Nonviolent Coordinating Committee (SNCC)- Memoranda and Reports (Copies), 1960-1967 (Box-folder 58:2)
  - Student Nonviolent Coordinating Committee (SNCC)- Minutes (Copies), 1960-1964 (Box-folder 58:3)
  - Student Nonviolent Coordinating Committee (SNCC)- Minutes (Copies), 1965-1967, n.d. (Box-folder 58:4)
  - Student Nonviolent Coordinating Committee (SNCC)- Miscellaneous, 1962-1966, 1982 (Box-folder 58:5)
  - Student Nonviolent Coordinating Committee (SNCC)- Raleigh Conference, 1960, 1990 (Box-folder 58:6)
  - Student Nonviolent Coordinating Committee (SNCC)- Press Releases, 1961-1976, n.d., News clippings and Printed. (Box-folder 58:7)
  - Student Nonviolent Coordinating Committee (SNCC)- Programs, 1960-1967, 1990, n.d. (Box-folder 58:8)
  - Student Nonviolent Coordinating Committee (SNCC) - Statement of Sergeant Joseph P. Grubisic, Chicago Police Department, c. 1969 ? (Box-folder 58:9)
  - Student Nonviolent Coordinating Committee (SNCC)-The Student Voice, 1962 April (Box-folder 58:10)
  - Student Nonviolent Coordinating Committee (SNCC)  Trinity College Conference We Shall Not Be Moved- Sessions 1-3, 1988 April 14-16 (Box-folder 58:11)
  - Student Nonviolent Coordinating Committee (SNCC)  Trinity College Conference We Shall Not Be Moved- Sessions 4-6, 1988 April 14-16 (Box-folder 58:12)
  - Student Nonviolent Coordinating Committee (SNCC)  Trinity College Conference We Shall Not Be Moved- Sessions 7-8, 1988 April 14-16 (Box-folder 59:1)
  - Student Nonviolent Coordinating Committee (SNCC)- Vietnam, 1965-1966, 1968 (Box-folder 59:2)
    Includes a copy of the open letter of James Forman to the New York Anti-War Conference of the Fifth Avenue Vietnam Peace Parade Committee.
  - Student Organization for Black Unity (Cleveland Sellers), 1969 (Box-folder 59:3)
  - Twenty-First Century Foundation, 1971-1977 (Box-folder 59:4)
  - United Negro College Fund, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 59:5)
  - Village Foundation, 1997 (Box-folder 59:6)
  - Voter Education Project, 1969 (Box-folder 59:7)
  - Voter Education Project, 1970 (Box-folder 59:8)
  - Voter Education Project, 1971 February-June (Box-folder 59:9)
  - Voter Education Project, 1971 July-December (Box-folder 59:10)
  - Voter Education Project, 1972 February-June (Box-folder 60:1)
  - Voter Education Project, 1972 July-December (Box-folder 60:2)
  - Voter Education Project, 1973 February-July (Box-folder 60:3)
  - Voter Education Project, 1973 August-1977 (Box-folder 60:4)
  - Voter Education Project, n.d. (Box-folder 60:5)
  - Voter Education Project- Minority Candidates in the South, 1975 (Box-folder 60:6)
  - Voter Education Project- Photographs of Tours in Alabama and Louisiana, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 60:7)
  - Voter Education Project- Press Releases and Statistics, 1964-1973 (Box-folder 60:8)
  - Voter Education Project- Reports concerning Andrew Young's 1972 Race for Congress and Runoff Primaries and Fair Representation for Blacks in Congress, 1973, 1984 (Box-folder 60:9)
  - Voter Registration Account, 1972 (Box-folder 60:10)
  - W through Z Organizations, 1969-1976 (Box-folder 60:11)
  - Washington Research Project, 1969 (Box-folder 60:12)
  - Young Men's Christian Association (YMCA), 1969-1976 (Box-folder 60:13)
  - Young Men On the Go, 1969 (Box-folder 60:14)
  - Youth Project of Vermont, Inc., 1969 (Box-folder 61:1)
  - Youth Citizenship Fund, Inc., 1972-1973 (Box-folder 61:2)
- Series IV: Invitations, Political Associates, and American Program Bureau Papers
  - American Program Bureau- Contracts, etc., 1968 July-September (Box-folder 61:3)
  - American Program Bureau- Contracts, etc., 1968 October-December (Box-folder 61:4)
  - American Program Bureau- Contracts, etc., 1969 January-April (Box-folder 61:5)
  - American Program Bureau- Contracts, etc., 1969 May-December (Box-folder 61:6)
  - American Program Bureau- Contracts, etc., 1970 (Box-folder 61:7)
  - American Program Bureau- Contracts, etc., 1971 January-June (Box-folder 61:8)
  - American Program Bureau- Contracts, etc., 1971 July-December (Box-folder 61:9)
  - American Program Bureau- Contracts, etc., 1972 (Box-folder 62:1)
  - American Program Bureau- Contracts, etc., 1973 (Box-folder 62:2)
  - American Program Bureau- Contracts, etc., 1974 (Box-folder 62:3)
  - American Program Bureau- Contracts, etc., 1975 (Box-folder 62:4)
  - American Program Bureau-Contracts, etc., 1976 (Box-folder 62:5)
  - American Program Bureau- Contracts, etc., 1977 (Box-folder 63:1)
  - American Program Bureau- Contracts, etc., 1978 (Box-folder 63:2)
  - American Program Bureau- Contracts, etc., 1979 (Box-folder 63:3)
  - American Program Bureau- Contracts, etc., 1980 (Box-folder 63:4)
  - American Program Bureau- Contracts, etc., 1981 (Box-folder 63:5)
  - American Program Bureau- Contracts, etc., 1988 (Box-folder 63:6)
  - American Program Bureau- Correspondence, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 63:7)
  - American Program Bureau- Correspondence, 1971 (Box-folder 63:8)
  - American Program Bureau- Correspondence, 1972-1975 (Box-folder 64:1)
  - American Program Bureau- Correspondence, 1976 (Box-folder 64:2)